Finding Aid for Joan F. Cuddihy papers, 1945-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Joan F. Cuddihy papers 1945-1972
Cuddihy, Joan F.
0.3 linear feet.
85118 Aa 2
Forest Hills, New York, resident. Personal correspondence from U. S. Supreme Court Justice Frank Murphy; also miscellaneous newspaper clippings and photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Joan F. Cuddihy (donor no. 5765 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Joan F. Cuddihy was engaged to be married to Supreme Court Justice Frank Murphy in 1949.
The Cuddihy collection consists of personal correspondence from U. S. Supreme Court Justice Frank Murphy. Also included are miscellaneous newspaper clippings and photographs.
Subjects:
Women--New York (State)--New York; Forest Hills (New York, N.Y.)
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Churches--Michigan--Harbor Beach.; Cuddihy, Joan F.; Dwellings--Michigan--Harbor Beach.; Funeral rites and ceremonies.; Harbor Beach (Mich.)--Churches.; Harbor Beach (Mich.)--Dwellings.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; Our Lady of Lake Huron Church (Harbor Beach, Mich.)
Contributors:
Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Correspondence and other papers
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from Frank Murphy
    - Undated and 1945 (Box 1)
    - 1946, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1947, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1948 (Box 1)
    - 1949 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from friends and Murphy family, 1945-1972 (Box 1)
    (include letters from Murphy's biographer Sidney Fine)
  - Copies of Correspondence to Frank Murphy, 1933-1949 (Box 1)
    (include letters from Arthur M. Schlesinger)
  - Journal articles about Murphy, 1959, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning death of Frank Murphy and of his engagement to Joan Cuddihy, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings (Box 1)
  - Memorabilia from Truman inauguration, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of the Murphy family home in Harbor Beach, Michigan; photos of Frank Murphy's funeral 1949 (Box 1)